1.Java8的新特性，支持Lambda表达式
    Lambda表达式用来代替功能接口。
    语法如下：
        (parameters)->expression
        (parameters)->{statements;}
        如：
        ()->5
        (x,y)->x+y
        (int x,int y)->x-y
        (String s)->System.out.println(s)


// 使用匿名内部类  
btn.setOnAction(new EventHandler<ActionEvent>() {  
          @Override  
          public void handle(ActionEvent event) {  
              System.out.println("Hello World!");   
          }  
    });  
// 或者使用 lambda expression  
btn.setOnAction(event -> System.out.println("Hello World!")); 

// 1.1使用匿名内部类  
new Thread(new Runnable() {  
    @Override  
    public void run() {  
        System.out.println("Hello world !");  
    }  
}).start();  
// 1.2使用 lambda expression  
new Thread(() -> System.out.println("Hello world !")).start();  


2. Double Brace Initializaiton
	example
		HashSet<String> set = new HashSet<String>(){{	// note that generic type must be specified, you cannot use new HashSet<>(){}
			add("hello");
			add("hi");
		}}
	the first brace defines a new AnonymousInnerClass
	the second brace defines a static block inside the AnonymousInnerClass
		codes in the static block will be executed when the class is loaded
		and an instance inner class has access to its enclosing class object
		so, you can do things to the enclosing class object, usually initializations, at this place

3. release your code
	deployment options
		local
			the entire application runs on the end-user's computer, 
				deployed as an executable JAR
		combination of local and remote
			distributed with a client portion running on the user's local system,
				connected to a server where other parts of the app are running
			RMI
		remote
			the entire java application runs on a server system
				with the client accessing the system through some non-Java means, probably a web browser
			Servlets
				code runs on the server
	JAR (Java Archive)
		bundles all the classes (actually classes are at the final state of development, JAR is just archiving them)
		by telling the JVM which class has the main() method inside the manifest, you make the JAR executable
		(IDE takes care of these)
	some installer program can detect whether JVM is installed in the client's system, and install it if not
		InstallShield, InstallAnywhere, DeployDirector
	



